Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive 1989-2004 MSS 191
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - DVD / The New Museum of Contemporary Art, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Expenses - Red Hot + Durban, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Expenses - Red Hot + Lagos (Restricted), 2000 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Family Affair (Restricted), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Fefe Na Efe (Restricted), [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Gentleman (Restricted), 2001 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 2000 - 2002 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 2000 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Invoices / Budget (Restricted), 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Lagos, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Lagos contacts, [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Lagos expenses, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Lagos release forms, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Marketing, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Me'Shell NdegéOcello session, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Mortensen mess, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - No Agreement!!, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Paul [Heck]'s expenses, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot 1, [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 3)
      Zip disk: MAC100, 100 MB.
    - Red Hot 2, [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 4)
      Zip disk: PC100, 100 MB.
    - Red Hot Organization, [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 5)
      Zip disk: 100 MB.
    - Sade "By Your Side", 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Shakara / Lady (Restricted), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Shuffering & Shmiling (Restricted), 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Signed (Restricted), 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Sorrow Tears + Blood (Restricted), 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Trouble Sleep; Yanga Wake Am (Restricted), 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Video releases (Restricted), 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Water No Get Enemy session / invoices (Restricted), 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Zombie, 2000-2002 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Ads - Red Hot + Riot, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Best Albums of 2002 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Online press, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Riot, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings, 2002 - 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings compiled by Music Corporation of America, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Press in magazines, 2000 - 2002 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Press release, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Red Hot + Riot: Encounters with AIDS in Africa; Red Hot Organization, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      DVD
    - Reviews, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs, [n.d.] (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Riot; MCA Records, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Series XIX: General Red Hot Organization
  - Subseries A: Administration Files, American Express folders contain account information. Same for Checks, Cheque books, Deposits, Monthly accounting statements, Padell Nadell etc, Martin Greene Ravden folders, Bank statement folders, Information Document Request folders
    amfAR stands for American Foundation for AIDS Research. (http://www.amfar.org)
    Financial files (receipts, bills, etc.) may have been processed on box level only.
    - "We're All In This Together", 1994 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 1994 payroll taxes (Restricted), 1994 - 1996 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Accounting, 1993 - 1994 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - ACT UP: Aids Coalition To Unleash Power, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Agreements, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Amazon.com auction, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - American Express, 1994 - 1995 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - American Express, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - American Express, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - American Express, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - American Express: Correspondence and Quarterly Management Reports, 1996 - 1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Annual "closed books" reports and accounts, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Arista Records, Inc., 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bank reconciliations - Checking, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Bank reconciliations - Multiple, 1996 - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Bank reconciliations - Signature Bank, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Bank statements - Chemical Bank, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bank statements - HSBC Bank, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Bank statements and checks - Republic National Bank, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Bank statements - Republic National Bank, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Bank statements - Signature Bank, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - BCL Entertainment Corp. (Merchandising), 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Bills (Restricted), 2001 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A--B, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: C, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: D--P, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): A--B, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): C, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): D--G, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid (Box #2): H--Z, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Bills, paid: C--D, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Bills, paid: E--F, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Bills, paid: G--N, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bills, paid: P, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Bills, paid: Q--Z, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bills, paid: A, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Bills, paid: B--N, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Bills, paid: O--W, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Bills, paid: A--C (Restricted), 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Bills, paid: D--U (Restricted), 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Blank forms, "List of Business Expenses", [n.d.] (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - BMG donation, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports, 1999-2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cash receipts and disbursements reports; check transaction reports, 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cellular One Savings Book, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Checks, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Checks, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Chemical Bank, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Cheque books, Barclays Bank, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Chrysalis Records / amfAR loan repayment, 1991-1995 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clark, Larry film treatment, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Restricted), 1996-1999 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - Miscellaneous (Restricted), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Davis Polk & Wardwell, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Dead Meat [Sue Coe], 1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Delaware corporation - Not-for-profit, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Deposit slips, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Deposit slips, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Deposit slips, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Deposit slips - HSBC Bank, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Deposit slips - Republic National Bank, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Deposit slips - Signature Bank, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Detailed ledger by job, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Dissolution of The Red Hot Organisation Limited (UK), 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - EasyPay tax reports (Restricted), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - ECD - paid bills, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Egan, Nick, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Exempt Organization Certifications, 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Expenses above and beyond, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Expenses: Federal Express /Messengers, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Feinstein Management, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Finances, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Financial matters - Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Financial reports, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Financial statement, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - First Institutional Securities, LLC, 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Fleet Bank - petty cash; statements, 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Form 990 - Grants, Allocations and Payments to Affiliates and Others, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - From Movieplay, [n.d.] (Box 23, Folder 24)
      SyQuest 200 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
    - Funding/collaboration requests from HIV/AIDS service organizations, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Funding application pack, Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, November 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - General Journal Transaction Edit List, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - General ledger, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - General ledger, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - General ledger, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - General ledger, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - General ledger, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - General ledger, 1999, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - General ledger, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Giancarlo & Glieberman, 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Government Money Market Mutual Fund, 1996-2002 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Grants, 2001-2002 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Income, 1994-1997 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Information Document Request (IRS), 1997 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Information request, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Insurance, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Intra-organization correspondence re: general accounts/cashflow, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Invitation list for Young Soul Rebels premiere, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Invoice approval requests/forms, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Invoices, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Invoices: "Not Entered", 2000-2002 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Contains invoices relating to Red Hot + Indigo and Red Hot + Riot.
    - Invoices: amfAR, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Invoices: Barclays Bank, [n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Invoices: Cinram International Inc., 2002 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Invoices: Inter-company (Restricted), 1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Invoices: Martin Greene Ravden, 1992 - 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Invoices: Paid, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Invoices: Red Hot & Movin', 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - IRS - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - IRS - Information for Application for Recognition of Exemption, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - June 93 - June 94 account, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Kaktus Valley, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - King Cole Inc. - Entity information, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - King Cole Inc. - Incorporation, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Landauer, Tracy (Balber Pickard Battistoni Maldonado & Van Der Tuin, PC), 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Lawyers Alliance for New York, 1993-2001 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Leases, 1990-1997 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Ledgers, 2000, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - License requests, 1991-2001 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - List of gay periodicals, [n.d.] (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Lounge $$$, 1998-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lounge - paid bills (Restricted), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - Company correspondence, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - UK correspondence, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Martin Greene Ravden - USA correspondence with UK re: 6/30/94, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Memos, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Messengers, 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Minolta Business Systems, Inc. Maintenance Supply Agreements; CBS Whitcom Purchase Agreement, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous literature, [n.d.] (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Money Market bank statements, 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Includes deposit tickets, statements, transfer requests, grant awardees' information and more.
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Monthly accounting statements, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Morrissey "England's Answer to the H-Bomb", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - MTV, 1998 - 1999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Native Tongues, 1991 - 1993 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Notes on operation of PAYE re: payments to casual and freelance staff in the Film Industry, 1990 - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Opening Entries Report, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Oppenheimer & Co., Inc., 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Organization cashflow, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Outlicensing, 1992 - 1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1998 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Oct - Nov 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), Feb - June 1999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Dec 1998 - Feb 1999 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Mar - May 1999 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), June - Sep 1999 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting), Oct - Dec 1999 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company (accounting) (Restricted), 2002 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company - reports, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Payroll / Taxes (Restricted), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Payroll - Unofficial file, "Francine's" (Restricted), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Payroll (Restricted), 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Permanent file, 1992-1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Includes press packets, information on grants awarded, organization structures, legal forms.
    - PolyGram Holding, Inc. - Back end advance, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Posting reports - Republic National Bank/HSBC Bank, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Posting reports - Signature Bank, 2001 - 2002 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Proposal (film), [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Ralph Lauren promotional CDs, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Receipts - Reimbursed (Restricted), 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Red Hot + Bothered / * Important Beat stills, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Content
      Apparently includes files on Beat Experience, America Is Dying Slowly and Red Hot + Bothered.
    - Red Hot #15, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      Includes files on Red Hot + Blue, Red Hot + Dance, No Alternative, Red Hot + Country, Red Hot + Cool, Beat Experience.
    - Red Hot AIDS Charitable Trust/London office, 1993-1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Red Hot Disk 1, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Red Hot Minis, 1990-1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Royalty statement - "We're All in This Together: A Benefit for AIDS", 1994 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Sebastian, Earle, [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Share certificate of John Carlin, 1994 - 1995 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Slogans, [n.d.] (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Statement of income and expenses, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Storage item list, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Strauss, Seymour (Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company), 1997 - 2003 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Summary of cash balances and related schedules of cash receipts and disbursements, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 (Restricted), 1994 - 1997 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Tax audit 12/31/94 - "Our take" (Restricted), 1993 - 1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Tax forms (Restricted), 1990 - 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Tax return filing instructions, prepared by Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Co., 1998 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Taxes - Foreign, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Trademarks, 1994-1999 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - UK Liquidation, 1995 - 1996 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - UK office: Correspondence, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Video tracking log: Misc., [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - W.A.D. Party '02, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Wire transfer requests/confirmations - Signature Bank (Restricted), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Women's Moves, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Womyn for Womyn: a lesbian resource centre, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - WTC Business Recovery Grant, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Zoo TV, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Art Against AIDS - On The Road, c.a. 1989 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Envelopes - Downtown Arts Festival, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Happy New Year from Red Hot Organization, c.a. 1994 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Information packet, c.a. 1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Invitations to "the heart of summer", [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Invitations to a party to honor The Red Hot Organization, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Postcards - Designs by David McDiarmid, commissioned by AIDS Council of NSW, (ACON) Australia, c.a. 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Postcards - Levi's Presents: A Month of Music, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings - The Condom Project (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings - General, 1993-1998 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Press clippings - General, 1994-2001 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Press clippings - Love in the 90's, 1995 - 1998 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Press clippings - Miscellaneous, 1991 - 1996 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Press clippings - Museums: New York, 1995-1996 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Press clippings - 10th Anniversary, 2000 - 2001 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings - Twentieth-Century Blues: The Songs of Noel Coward, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Press masters, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Press master samples, c.a. 1998 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Press release - 10th Anniversary (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Red Hot Again Photography Auction catalogue, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Season's Greetings card, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Stickers - Red Hot Organization, [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Stickers - True Love (in association with The Condom Project) (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Negatives: "[Suite] pictures Mark Valentine", [n.d.] (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - All Access: The Horde Festival CD-ROM, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Red Hot & Skin; PonyCanyon Entertainment (Singapore), 1993 (Box 29, Folder 35)
      Double audio compact disc
    - We're All in This Together; GRP Records, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Subseries E: Awards
    - VH1 Honors, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Oversize Series I: Red Hot + Blue, 1990
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material, 1990
    - Posters - Red Hot + Blue, [n.d.] (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Press clippings, 1990 - 1991 (Box [46])
    - Promotional single: "Night and Day," U2; Island Records Ltd., 1990 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 45 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt order form, [n.d.] (Box [46])
  - Subseries B: Red Hot + Dance
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master One, December 15, 1991 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0155A)
      Format: 2 inch Quad
      TRT: Unknown
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master One - Recording Notes, 1991 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0155B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Two, December 15, 1991 (Media 60, Media ID: 191.0156A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Two - Recording Notes, 1991 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0156B)
    - Red Hot + Dance - 2 inch Quad Master Three, December 15, 1991 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0157A)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Master Three - Recording Notes, 1991 (Box TBA, Folder ID: 191.0157B)
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0158)
      Format: 1/4 inch Open Reel
      TRT: [4 mins 36 secs]
    - Matthew Sweet - Super Deformed - 1/4 inch Open Reel, October 21, 1993 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0159)
      TRT: [3 mins 55 secs]
    - Urge Overkill - Take A Walk - 1/4 inch Open Reel, November 2, 1993 (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0160)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder One, [1991-1993] (Box TBA)
    - Red Hot + Dance - Miscellaneous Paperwork, Folder Two, [1991-1993] (Box TBA)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 1 of 5, November 30, 1991 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0161)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 2 of 5, November 30, 1991 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0162)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 3 of 5, November 30, 1991 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0163)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 4 of 5, November 30, 1991 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0164)
    - Red Hot + Dance - AIDS Dancathon - 2 inch Quad, Reel 5 of 5, November 30, 1991 (Box 61, Media ID: 191.0165)
      - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 1 of 2, Unknown (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0166)
    - Red Hot + Dance 9PP4 - 1/4 inch Open Reel, 2 of 2, Unknown (Box 60, Media ID: 191.0167)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Limited edition picture disc: "Well, Did You Evah!" by Deborah Harry & Iggy Pop; Chrysalis Records Ltd., 1990 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog; 12 in.
    - Red Hot + Blue, 1990 (Box 42)
      Laser disc
    - Single: "I've Got You Under My Skin," Neneh Cherry; Circa Records, 1990 (Box 42)
    - Sweatshirts - David Wojnarowicz artwork and text, c.a. 1990 (Box 30)
    - T-shirt - safe sex is hot sex, [n.d.] (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0001)
- Oversize Series II: Red Hot + Dance
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1991 (Box [46])
    - Promotional limited edition four record DJ box set; Epic Records, 1992 (Box 42)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Double A-Side: Crystal Waters / Sabrina Johnston - "Gypsy Woman" / "Peace;" Epic Records, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Red Hot + Dance double album; Columbia, 1992 (Box 42)
    - Remixes of "Too Funky," "Too Jazzy" and "Crazyman Dance," George Michael; Columbia, 1992 (Box 42)
      Sound Disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - Single: "The Boy From Ipanema," Crystal Waters; verve Records, 1996 (Box 42)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
      Sound disc: Analog, 33 1/3 rpm; 12 in.
    - T-shirt - Red Hot + Dance, 1993 (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0002)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple, [n.d.] (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0003)
    - T-shirts - safe sex is hot sex, male couple close-up, [n.d.] (Box 31, Object ID: 191.2.0004)
- Oversize Series III: No Alternative